We're going to be learning how to configure organizational settings including security, privacy and profile in Microsoft 365 admin center.
So, when you create a new Microsoft 365 admin center tenant, definitely you want to actually customize your organizational settings.
So, if I go to under my settings here you can see we have all settings, so just click on it.
And from all settings we have services security and privacy and then we have organizational profile.
So, let me first of all go to organizational profile.
Here you can see we got all the customized for example, we can decide to add some help desk information.
You can see I want to add some help desk information.
Should in case your users want to contact the help desk to be able, when they open their Microsoft 365, they will be able to see that information.
Which of course you can see streamlives us support by adding the organization contact information to the Office 365 helping.
So, if you have appear beneath the default help topics.
So, when I go to Office 365 or the opening Office 365 app, you can see it's going to actually appear beneath the default help topics.
So, for example, I can just decide to just put let me just put go.
Mobile help desk, and here we can just set a phone on my is just plus three two four one two three four five six seven.
And then the email I can just decide to say what the email is going to be info at kelvil.com.
And here we can put help desk website, we can help puts the website of kelvil.com.
And then mind you, you need to put the HTTP and then a slice.
Here we can just add the website, let me just copy this and then put it there.
So, let's just click save and this information will be saved and also we can decided to add organization information.
You can see we have a default information that was actually and when we create this tenant, the information we entered is going to be shown here.
So, here you can see all my information, but at the same time you can decide to change the telephone number 15 telephone number is not correct and also your address.
So, let me just close that.
So, we also have some all our information we got all this.
I'm going to figure out here.
Well, let me go back again to security and privacy.
On the security and privacy here, for example, we can decide to set the privacy statement of your organization, we can decide to go to the privacy profile and then enter the privacy.
For example, if we have a privacy statement, you can just copy the link and then put it here and then enter your organization on privacy contact.
So, we can tell the specific contact which of course, issue, anyone can contact if there's any issues or someone wants to ask or request more information about your privacy.
So, these are how you actually add some of your organizational, configure some of your national settings or modify some of your business.
So, these national settings in Microsoft 365 admin center.